[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who was the host of the 72nd Academy Awards ceremony held on March 26, 2000?", "correct_answer": "Billy Crystal", "incorrect_answers": ["Ellen DeGeneres", "Steve Martin", "Robin Williams"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of Oprah Winfreys character in the 1985 drama movie The Color Purple directed by Steven Spielberg?", "correct_answer": "Sofia", "incorrect_answers": ["Celie", "Miss Millie", "Nettie"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which part  of the Loch Ness monster is most noteworthy according to people who claim to have seen it?", "correct_answer": "Neck", "incorrect_answers": ["Hair", "Eyes", "Teeth"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "From the 1600s to the 1800s, the British and Dutch were interested in Borneo because they wanted control of this resource.", "correct_answer": "Pepper", "incorrect_answers": ["Salt", "Coffee", "Tea"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In this Indo-European language, which has 11 vowels and 35 consonants, postpositions are used instead of prepositions.", "correct_answer": "Hindi", "incorrect_answers": ["Cantonese", "Armenian", "Arabic"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How many new species of animals and plants were discovered on Borneo between July 2005 and September 2006?", "correct_answer": "52", "incorrect_answers": ["None", "121", "3"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In this board game moves are determined by dice rolls. Each player attempts to move around the board, from point to point, to get home.", "correct_answer": "Backgammon", "incorrect_answers": ["Chess", "Go", "Cribbage"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What does XML stand for?", "correct_answer": "extensible markup language", "incorrect_answers": ["excellent markup language", "extensive markup language", "easy markup language"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What animal cell helped prove that membrane proteins drift?", "correct_answer": "Mouse", "incorrect_answers": ["Dog", "Fish", "Monkey"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How far along are you approximately, when you feel the baby move for the first time?", "correct_answer": "20 weeks", "incorrect_answers": ["10 weeks", "35 weeks", "2 weeks"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This 1940 movie was Alfred Hitchcocks first American project, and won an Academy Award for Best Picture.", "correct_answer": "Rebecca", "incorrect_answers": ["Under Capricorn", "Shadow of a Doubt", "Notorious"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these statements is not true about the vision of bats?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Most smaller bat species are blind.", "All bat species are able to detect UV light.", "All bat species have underdeveloped eyesight."]}]